Guide to the Robert Maynard Hutchins Papers 1884-2000
University of Chicago Library
- Series II: Correspondence
  - Newell, Mrs. J. P., 1934-1937 (Box 178, Folder 7)
  - Newman, 1937-1950 (Box 178, Folder 8)
  - Newman, Paul, 1966-1973 (Box 178, Folder 9)
  - Newsday, 1959-1960 (Box 178, Folder 10)
  - Newsom, Earl, 1930-1945 (Box 178, Folder 11)
  - Next Voter, The, May 1949-May 1950 (Box 178, Folder 12)
  - Neylan, John F., 1939-1945 (Box 178, Folder 13)
  - Niebuhr, Reinhold, 1946-1950 (Box 178, Folder 14)
  - Nendorff, John H., 1941-1944 (Box 179, Folder 1)
  - Nitze, William, 1940-1948 (Box 179, Folder 2)
  - No-Frontier News Service, 1941 (Box 179, Folder 3)
  - Nobel Prize, 1943-1950 (Box 179, Folder 4)
  - Non-Sectarian, 1938-1940 (Box 179, Folder 5)
  - Non-Sectarian Anti-Nazi League, 1937-1939 (Box 179, Folder 6)
  - Non-Sectarian Foundation for Refugee Children, 1939-1940 (Box 179, Folder 7)
  - Norlin, George, 1938-1939 (Box 179, Folder 8)
  - Norris, 1941-1947 (Box 179, Folder 9)
  - Norris, Charles G., 1939-1940 (Box 179, Folder 10)
  - North American Film Corporation, 1939 (Box 179, Folder 11)
  - North Carolina, 1932-1950 (Box 179, Folder 12)
  - North Central Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, 1942 (Box 179, Folder 13)
  - North Shore, 1938-1948 (Box 179, Folder 14)
  - North-Northeastern, 1938-1950 (Box 179, Folder 15)
  - Northern-Northwestern, 1939-1949 (Box 179, Folder 16)
  - Northwestern, 1930-1938 (Box 179, Folder 17)
  - Northwestern University, 1938-1951 (Box 179, Folder 18)
  - Notre Dame, University of, 1938-1950 (Box 180, Folder 1)
  - Noyes, Seldon, 1938-1944 (Box 180, Folder 2)
  - Nuveen, John, 1939-1950 (Box 180, Folder 3)
  - Nyjordet, Berner E., 1942 (Box 180, Folder 4)
  - Oak Park, 1936-1950 (Box 180, Folder 5)
  - Oberlin College, 1932-1947 (Box 180, Folder 6)
  - Oberlin College, 1948-1951 (Box 180, Folder 7)
  - O'Brien, 1937-1950 (Box 180, Folder 8)
  - O'Connor, 1938-1950 (Box 180, Folder 9)
  - Ogan, R. W., 1942 (Box 180, Folder 10)
  - Ogburn, William F., 1936-1948 (Box 180, Folder 11)
  - O'Hare, John F., 1936-1939 (Box 180, Folder 12)
  - Ohio, 1929-1937 (Box 180, Folder 13)
  - Ohio, 1938-1950 (Box 180, Folder 14)
  - Oklahoma, 1939-1949 (Box 181, Folder 1)
  - Olivet College, 1934-1939 (Box 181, Folder 2)
  - Olsen-Olson, 1939-1950 (Box 181, Folder 3)
  - Olson, O. D., 1942-1954 (Box 181, Folder 4)
  - Olson, Warren E., 1969-1971 (Box 181, Folder 5)
  - O'Meara, Joseph, Jr., 1939-1948 (Box 181, Folder 6)
  - Ontario Secondary School Teachers Association, 1947-1948 (Box 181, Folder 7)
  - Oregon, 1939-1947 (Box 181, Folder 8)
  - Orr, 1938-1944 (Box 181, Folder 9)
  - Osborn - Osborne, 1940-1950 (Box 181, Folder 10)
  - Osborn, Fairfield, 1923-1961 (Box 181, Folder 11)
  - Osborn, Fairfield (Our Plundered Planet), 1948 [1/2] (Box 181, Folder 12)
  - Osborn, Fairfield (Our Plundered Planet), 1948 [2/2] (Box 181, Folder 13)
  - Osman, John, 1958-1962 (Box 181, Folder 14)
  - Ostrow, Seniel, 1961-1976 (Box 181, Folder 15)
  - Otis, 1941-1944 (Box 181, Folder 16)
  - Ottawa, 1939-1940 (Box 181, Folder 17)
  - Owen-Owens, 1938-1950 (Box 181, Folder 18)
  - Oxford University Press, 1938-1950 (Box 181, Folder 19)
  - Paepcke, Walter, 1940-1950 (Box 182, Folder 1)
  - Paepcke, Walter and Elizabeth, 1940-1976 (Box 182, Folder 2)
  - Palmer, 1939-1950 (Box 182, Folder 3)
  - Palmer, Walter, 1939 (Box 182, Folder 4)
  - Pan American, 1939-1945 (Box 182, Folder 5)
  - Parent - Park, 1937-1951 (Box 182, Folder 6)
  - Parker, 1929-1949 (Box 182, Folder 7)
  - Parr - Parran, 1939-1943 (Box 182, Folder 8)
  - Parten, Jubal R., 1957-1971 (Box 182, Folder 9)
  - Parten, Jubal R., 1971-1974 (Box 182, Folder 10)
  - Parten, Jubal R., 1975 (Box 182, Folder 11)
  - Parvin Foundation, 1961-1962 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Parvin Foundation, 1962-1965 (Box 183, Folder 2)
  - Parvin Foundation, 1966-1967 (Box 183, Folder 3)
  - Parvin Foundation, 1967-1969 (Box 183, Folder 4)
  - Parvin Foundation, 1969-1973 (Box 183, Folder 5)
  - Parvin Foundation, 1975-1977 (Box 183, Folder 6)
  - Patterson, 1936-1950 (Box 183, Folder 7)
  - Pauling, Linus, 1958-1969 (Box 184, Folder 1)
  - Peace, 1938-1950 (Box 184, Folder 2)
  - Peace, 1950-1951 (Box 184, Folder 3)
  - Peacock, 1943-1947 (Box 184, Folder 4)
  - Pearson, Sigfrid, 1937-1938 (Box 184, Folder 5)
  - Peiser - Pembroke, 1936-1945 (Box 184, Folder 6)
  - Pence, Jack, 1935-1938 (Box 184, Folder 7)
  - Pennsylvania, 1929-1950 (Box 184, Folder 8)
  - People's 1939-1951 (Box 184, Folder 9)
  - Peoria, 1932-1945 (Box 184, Folder 10)
  - Pepsi Cola Company, 1940-1942 (Box 184, Folder 11)
  - Percy, Charles, 1958-1967 (Box 184, Folder 12)
  - Perkins, 1936-1948 (Box 185, Folder 1)
  - Permissions, 1950 (Box 185, Folder 2)
  - Perry, 1939-1950 (Box 185, Folder 3)
  - Perry, John L., 1966-1967 (Box 185, Folder 4)
  - Perry, John L., 1967-1968 (Box 185, Folder 5)
  - Perry, John L., 1968-1969 (Box 185, Folder 6)
  - Perry, John L., 1969-1970 (Box 185, Folder 7)
  - Persoff, Al, 1944-1948 (Box 185, Folder 8)
  - Peters, 1943-1951 (Box 185, Folder 9)
  - Peterson, 1943-1949 (Box 185, Folder 10)
  - Pettit, B. M., 1937-1941 (Box 185, Folder 11)
  - Pfeffer, J. Alan, 1937-1938 (Box 185, Folder 12)
  - Phelan, Gerald B., 1944-1949 (Box 185, Folder 13)
  - Phelps, 1939-1951 (Box 185, Folder 14)
  - Phelps Association, 1923-1941 (Box 186, Folder 1)
  - Phelps Association, 1923-1941 (Box 186, Folder 2)
  - Phelps Association, 1929-1951 (Box 186, Folder 3)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1929-1940 (Box 186, Folder 4)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1941-1951 (Box 186, Folder 5)
  - New York Address, 1940-1941 (Box 186, Folder 6)
  - Phi Beta Kappa - Yale Address, 1939-1940 (Box 186, Folder 7)
  - Phi Delta Kappa, 1938-1948 (Box 186, Folder 8)
  - Phi Delta Phi, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 9)
  - Phi Delta Theta, 1940 (Box 187, Folder 1)
  - Phi Kappa Phi, 1939 (Box 187, Folder 2)
  - Philadelphia, 1936-1950 (Box 187, Folder 3)
  - Phillips, 1942-1951 (Box 187, Folder 4)
  - Photographs, 1934-1951 (Box 187, Folder 5)
  - Pierce, Martin, 1958 (Box 187, Folder 6)
  - Pike, James A., 1966-1976 (Box 187, Folder 7)
  - Platt, Livingston, 1923-1925 (Box 187, Folder 8)
  - Poland, 1938-1949 (Box 187, Folder 9)
  - Polanyi, Michael, 1961-1962 (Box 187, Folder 10)
  - Policy Holders' Service Bureau, 1951 (Box 187, Folder 11)
  - Political Issues, 1931-1932 [1/2] (Box 187, Folder 12)
  - Political Issues, 1931-1932 (Box 187, Folder 13)
  - Pollock, 1939-1943 (Box 187, Folder 14)
  - Pope, James W., 1941-1949 (Box 187, Folder 15)
  - Porter, 1938-1950 (Box 188, Folder 1)
  - Posoviec, Stephen S., 1941 (Box 188, Folder 2)
  - Post War World Council, 1942-1949 (Box 188, Folder 3)
  - Potter - Potter, Milton, 1932-1948 (Box 188, Folder 4)
  - Powell - Powell, Thomas Reed, 1939-1948 (Box 188, Folder 5)
  - Poynter, Nelson P., 1940 (Box 188, Folder 6)
  - Pratt, Charles, 1923 (Box 188, Folder 7)
  - Preece, Warren E., 1966-1967 (Box 188, Folder 8)
  - Preece, Warren E., 1967 (Box 188, Folder 9)
  - Preece, Warren E., 1968-1969 (Box 188, Folder 10)
  - Prentis, H. W., Jr., 1943 (Box 188, Folder 11)
  - Presbyterian, 1939-1951 (Box 188, Folder 12)
  - President's house (includes plans of gardens), 1936-1937 (Box 188, Folder 13)
  - President's report, 1938-1939 (Box 188, Folder 14)
  - President's report, 1939-1940 (Box 188, Folder 15)
  - President's report, 1940-1941 (Box 188, Folder 16)
  - President's report, 1941-1943 (Box 189, Folder 1)
  - President's report, 1942 (Box 189, Folder 2)
  - President's report, 1943-1944 (Box 189, Folder 3)
  - President's report, 1944-1945 (Box 189, Folder 4)
  - President's report, 1945 (Box 189, Folder 5)
  - President's report, 1945-1946 (Box 189, Folder 6)
  - President's report, 1946-1948 (Box 189, Folder 7)
  - Preston, W. G., Jr., 1930-1941 (Box 189, Folder 8)
  - Price - Price, Maurice, 1938-1950 (Box 189, Folder 9)
  - Prince, Theodore, 1939 (Box 189, Folder 10)
  - Princeton University, 1934-1946 (Box 189, Folder 11)
  - Private Schools Association - Professional, 1938-1948 (Box 189, Folder 12)
  - Pressey, Sidney L., 1943-1946 (Box 190, Folder 1)
  - Probst, George E., 1960-1962 (Box 190, Folder 2)
  - Programs International/National Lecture Bureau, 1962-1969 (Box 190, Folder 3)
  - Progress Guide - Progressive, 1944-1951 (Box 190, Folder 4)
  - Progressive Education Association, 1933-1943 (Box 190, Folder 5)
  - Project Public Information, 1967-1968 (Box 190, Folder 6)
  - President - Proviso, 1938-1941 (Box 190, Folder 7)
  - Public Administration Clearing House, 1938-1940 (Box 190, Folder 8)
  - Public Administration Clearing House, 1940-1943 (Box 190, Folder 9)
  - Public Administration Clearing House, 1943-1948 (Box 190, Folder 10)
  - Public Administration Clearing House, 1936-1939 (Box 190, Folder 11)
  - Public Administration Clearing House, 1938-1939 (Box 191, Folder 1)
  - Public Administration Clearing House, 1941-1951 (Box 191, Folder 2)
  - Publicity, 1929 (Box 191, Folder 3)
  - Pulse, 1938 and undated (Box 191, Folder 4)
  - Purdue University, 1931-1949 (Box 191, Folder 5)
  - Pye, Ernest, 1938-1949 (Box 191, Folder 6)
  - Quantrell, Ernest E., 1938-1950 (Box 191, Folder 7)
  - Quincy Women's City Club, 1937-1938 (Box 191, Folder 8)
  - Quisenberry, T. Edwin, 1938-1939 (Box 191, Folder 9)
  - Rachlin, Edgar Lewis, 1939-1948 (Box 191, Folder 10)
  - Radio, 1929-1932 (Box 191, Folder 11)
  - Radio, 1932-1942 (Box 191, Folder 12)
  - Radio, 1942-1950 (Box 191, Folder 13)
  - Radio Address - "America and the War," 1941 (Box 191, Folder 14)
  - Radio Address - "Atomic Energy: Peace or War with Soviet Russia," 1946 (Box 191, Folder 15)
  - Radio Address - "Education and Democracy," 1939 (Box 192, Folder 1)
  - Radio Address - "Education in Independence," 1930 (Box 192, Folder 2)
  - Radio recording, 1940-1946 (Box 192, Folder 3)
  - Radio - Raing, 1937-1950 (Box 192, Folder 4)
  - Randall, Clarence B., 1935-1949 (Box 192, Folder 5)
  - Randolph - Random House, 1937-1950 (Box 192, Folder 6)
  - Randon, Peter C., 1941-1942 (Box 192, Folder 7)
  - Raner, Guy H., Jr., 1941-1950 (Box 192, Folder 8)
  - Rapoport, Bernard, 1966-1977 (Box 192, Folder 9)
  - Rappleye, Willard C., 1939-1942 (Box 192, Folder 10)
  - Rattner, Herbert, 1939-1945 (Box 192, Folder 11)
  - Ray, 1937-1947 (Box 192, Folder 12)
  - Reader's Digest, 1938-1950 (Box 192, Folder 13)
  - Reddick, John F., 1946 (Box 192, Folder 14)
  - Redfield, 1936-1950 (Box 192, Folder 15)
  - Redfield, Robert (lectures), 1958-1966 (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - Reed, Edward, 1961-1969 (Box 193, Folder 2)
  - Reiner, Kenneth, 1960-1966 (Box 193, Folder 3)
  - Rankin, 1940-1951 (Box 193, Folder 4)
  - Restoration of 4-Year A.B., 1953 (Box 193, Folder 5)
  - Rice, 1931-1948 (Box 193, Folder 6)
  - Rich, 1938-1940 (Box 193, Folder 7)
  - Richards, Howard, 1961-1976 (Box 193, Folder 8)
  - Richards, I. A., 1940-1947 (Box 193, Folder 9)
  - Richardson, 1940-1950 (Box 193, Folder 10)
  - Rickower, H. G., 1958-1959 (Box 193, Folder 11)
  - Rieff, Philip, 1958-1975 (Box 193, Folder 12)
  - Riezler, Kurt, 1943-1951 (Box 193, Folder 13)
  - Rippy, J. Fred, 1942-1950 (Box 193, Folder 14)
  - Ritchie-Calder, 1968-1976 (Box 193, Folder 15)
  - Roberts, 1931-1948 (Box 194, Folder 1)
  - Robertson, 1939-1950 (Box 194, Folder 2)
  - Robinson, 1939-1950 (Box 194, Folder 3)
  - Rochester, 1938-1947 (Box 194, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, 1937-1945 (Box 194, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller Family, 1929-1973 (Box 194, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller, John D., Jr., 1929-1947 (Box 194, Folder 7)
  - Rockmore, Irving (Associates), 1953-1954 (Box 194, Folder 8)
  - Rogers, 1938-1950 (Box 194, Folder 9)
  - Rogers, James - Rogers, Lindsay, 1936-1939 (Box 194, Folder 10)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1940-1950 (Box 194, Folder 11)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, 1933-1948 (Box 194, Folder 12)
  - Roosevelt, General Theodore, 1934-1945 (Box 194, Folder 13)
  - Roper, Elmo, 1957-1965 (Box 194, Folder 14)
  - Roper, Elmo, 1966-1973 (Box 195, Folder 1)
  - Rosenwald, Lessing J., 1929-1950 (Box 195, Folder 2)
  - Rosenwald Fund, 1934-1938 (Box 195, Folder 3)
  - Rosenwald Fund, 1938-1948 (Box 195, Folder 4)
  - Rosenwald, William, 1936-1940 (Box 195, Folder 5)
  - Ross, 1938-1950 (Box 195, Folder 6)
  - Rosten, Leo, 1952-1970 (Box 195, Folder 7)
  - Rotary Club, 1929-1940 (Box 195, Folder 8)
  - Rotary Club, 1941-1950 (Box 195, Folder 9)
  - Rothschild, Maurine and Robert, 1975-1977 (Box 195, Folder 10)
  - Rouse, Eugene F., 1934-1944 (Box 195, Folder 11)
  - Royal Society of St. George, 1942-1948 (Box 195, Folder 12)
  - Rubican, Raymond, 1937-1949 (Box 196, Folder 1)
  - Rubin, Arthur H. L., 1936-1951 (Box 196, Folder 2)
  - Ruddock, Albert, 1959-1961 (Box 196, Folder 3)
  - Ruml, Beardsley, 1931-1950 (Box 196, Folder 4)
  - Ruml, Beardsley, 1956-1960 (Box 196, Folder 5)
  - Russell, 1938-1950 (Box 196, Folder 6)
  - Russell, Bertrand, 1938-1941 (Box 196, Folder 7)
  - Russell, Paul and Carroll, 1953-1976 (Box 196, Folder 8)
  - Saboia de Madeiros, Roberto, 1945-1950 (Box 196, Folder 9)
  - Sachar, Abram L., 1959-1963 (Box 196, Folder 10)
  - Sachs, 1940-1947 (Box 196, Folder 11)
  - Sacred Heart, 1941-1942 (Box 196, Folder 12)
  - St. Augustine - St. Regis, 1937-1951 (Box 196, Folder 13)
  - St. Thomas - St. Xavier, 1937-1950 (Box 196, Folder 14)
  - St. John's College, 1937-1938 (Box 197, Folder 1)
  - St. John's College, 1939-1940 (Box 197, Folder 2)
  - St. John's College, 1941-1945 (Box 197, Folder 3)
  - St. John's College, 1945-1950 (Box 197, Folder 4)
  - St. John's College - Board of Visitors and Governors, 1937-1945 (Box 197, Folder 5)
  - St. Louis, 1938-1951 (Box 197, Folder 6)
  - St. Mary of the Springs College, 1937-1948 (Box 197, Folder 7)
  - Salomon, Irving, 1953-1976 (Box 197, Folder 8)
  - San Marino Realty, Co., 1950-1951 (Box 198, Folder 1)
  - Santa Barbara Adult Education Program, 1962-1963 (Box 198, Folder 2)
  - Sargent, 1935-1951 (Box 198, Folder 3)
  - Sarnoff, David, 1938-1939 (Box 198, Folder 4)
  - Saturday Evening Post, 1946-1951 (Box 198, Folder 5)
  - Saturday Evening Post - "Blueprint for Wartime Education," 1942 (Box 198, Folder 6)
  - Saturday Evening Post - "Blueprint for Wartime Education," 1942 (Box 198, Folder 7)
  - Saturday Review, 1938-1950 (Box 198, Folder 8)
  - Schleh, Teresa, 1951 (Box 198, Folder 9)
  - Schmidt, Lawrence J., 1936-1950 (Box 198, Folder 10)
  - Schneider, Franz, 1938-1951 (Box 198, Folder 11)
  - Scholastic magazine, 1932-1947 (Box 198, Folder 12)
  - School, 1939-1948 (Box 198, Folder 13)
  - School Board Action, 1932-1933 (Box 199, Folder 1)
  - School Board Action, 1933-1935 (Box 199, Folder 2)
  - School Board Action - General, 1933 (Box 199, Folder 3)
  - Schuster, M. Lincoln, 1952-1965 (Box 199, Folder 4)
  - Schwab, Joseph Jackson, 1953-1976 (Box 199, Folder 5)
  - Schweitzer, Albert, 1954 (Box 199, Folder 6)
  - Science Hill School, 1937-1939 (Box 199, Folder 7)
  - Scott, 1938-1950 (Box 199, Folder 8)
  - Scott, Malcolm, 1933-1950 (Box 199, Folder 9)
  - Scribner's, 1932-1950 (Box 199, Folder 10)
  - Second National Bank, New Haven, 1929-1930 (Box 199, Folder 11)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission, 1937-1938 (Box 200, Folder 1)
  - Seeley, John R., 1966-1972 (Box 200, Folder 2)
  - Seitner, Esther, 1962-1964 (Box 200, Folder 3)
  - Selig, Lester and Veva, 1953-1969 (Box 200, Folder 4)
  - Selznick, Philip, 1960-1975 (Box 200, Folder 5)
  - Senate Candidacy, 1953-1955 (Box 200, Folder 6)
  - Sevareid, Eric - Interview, 1975 [1/3] (Box 200, Folder 7)
  - Sevareid, Eric - Interview, 1975 [2/3] (Box 200, Folder 8)
  - Sevareid, Eric - Interview, 1975 [3/3] (Box 200, Folder 9)
  - Shane, Joseph D., 1960-1972 (Box 200, Folder 10)
  - Shapiro, 1941-1951 (Box 200, Folder 11)
  - Sharp, 1941-1948 (Box 200, Folder 12)
  - Sheinbaum, Stanley, 1960-1977 (Box 201, Folder 1)
  - Shiebler, Howard A., 1946 (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Short, 1938-1939 (Box 201, Folder 3)
  - Shultz, 1941 (Box 201, Folder 4)
  - Shuster, George N., 1955-1967 (Box 201, Folder 5)
  - Skewes-Cox, Bennet and Mary, 1964-1969 (Box 201, Folder 6)
  - Skirbal, Jack and Audrey, 1958-1977 (Box 201, Folder 7)
  - Smith, Herman Dunlap, 1951-1977 (Box 201, Folder 8)
  - Snell, Lenore (Eleanor) Shea, 1949-1950 (Box 201, Folder 9)
  - Sigerist, Henry E., 1938-1946 (Box 201, Folder 10)
  - Silverman, 1941-1949 (Box 201, Folder 11)
  - Simmons, 1938-1950 (Box 201, Folder 12)
  - Simon and Schuster, 1936-1948 (Box 201, Folder 13)
  - Simon and Schuster, 1949-1951 (Box 201, Folder 14)
  - Simon - Simons, 1941-1950 (Box 202, Folder 1)
  - Slesinger, Donald, 1929-1949 (Box 202, Folder 2)
  - Smith, 1929-1937 (Box 202, Folder 3)
  - Smith, 1938-1950 (Box 202, Folder 4)
  - Smith, 1939-1951 (Box 202, Folder 5)
  - Smith, Rennie, 1937-1939 (Box 202, Folder 6)
  - Smith, T. V., 1938-1950 (Box 202, Folder 7)
  - Social Frontier, 1934-1937 (Box 202, Folder 8)
  - Social Invitations, 1936-1937 (Box 202, Folder 9)
  - Society, 1938-1950 (Box 203, Folder 1)
  - Society for the Advancement of the General Welfare, 1936-1937 (Box 203, Folder 2)
  - South, 1938-1951 (Box 203, Folder 3)
  - South Bend Teachers Federation, 1939 (Box 203, Folder 4)
  - South Carolina Education Association, 1937 (Box 203, Folder 5)
  - South Dakota, 1938-1944 (Box 203, Folder 6)
  - South Shore Country Club, 1937-1949 (Box 203, Folder 7)
  - Southern, 1938-1951 (Box 203, Folder 8)
  - Southern Association of College and Secondary Schools, 1931-1940 (Box 203, Folder 9)
  - Southern Conference on Education, 1930 (Box 203, Folder 10)
  - Southwestern, 1939-1949 (Box 203, Folder 11)
  - Spector, Lawrence, 1959-1963 (Box 203, Folder 12)
  - Spencer, 1938-1946 (Box 203, Folder 13)
  - Spencer Foundation (Thomas James), 1963-1976 (Box 203, Folder 14)
  - Springfield, 1935-1950 (Box 203, Folder 15)
  - Square Table Club, 1937 (Box 203, Folder 16)
  - Stark, Harold - Stark, H. J. Lutcher, 1933-1943 (Box 203, Folder 17)
  - Stark - Starke, 1939-1944 (Box 204, Folder 1)
  - Stephens College, 1933-1949 (Box 204, Folder 2)
  - Stephens College - The Women's Foundation, 1941-1943 (Box 204, Folder 3)
  - Stephens College - The Women's Foundation, 1943-1944 (Box 204, Folder 4)
  - Stern, 1929-1951 (Box 204, Folder 5)
  - Stern, David, 1951 (Box 204, Folder 6)
  - Stevens, 1939-1951 (Box 204, Folder 7)
  - Stevens and Co., 1923-1926 (Box 204, Folder 8)
  - Stevenson, 1939-1945 (Box 204, Folder 9)
  - Stevenson, Adlai, 1931-1951 (Box 204, Folder 10)
  - Stevenson, Adlai, 1951-1960 (Box 204, Folder 11)
  - Stevenson, Adlai, 1960-1967 (Box 205, Folder 1)
  - Stevenson, Adlai - Memorial Fund, 1966-1972 (Box 205, Folder 2)
  - Stewart, 1939-1950 (Box 205, Folder 3)
  - Stewart, Edna (Celebrity management/National Lecture Bureau), 1957-1973 (Box 205, Folder 4)
  - Stoddard, George, 1953-1974 (Box 205, Folder 5)
  - Stokes, Frederick A., Co., 1938-1940 (Box 205, Folder 6)
  - Stoltenberg, Thomas R., 1944 (Box 205, Folder 7)
  - Store, 1940-1948 (Box 205, Folder 8)
  - Storke, Thomas M., 1959-1970 (Box 205, Folder 9)
  - Stouffer, Vernon, 1948 (Box 205, Folder 10)
  - Straus, Robert K., 1954-1974 (Box 205, Folder 11)
  - Stuart, 1937-1950 (Box 205, Folder 12)
  - Stuart, R. Douglas, Jr., 1939-1942 (Box 205, Folder 13)
  - Student, 1939-1951 (Box 206, Folder 1)
  - Student American Medical Association, 1968 (Box 206, Folder 2)
  - Supreme Court, 1937 (Box 206, Folder 3)
  - Survey Associates, Inc., 1938-1949 (Box 206, Folder 4)
  - Suspense Account, 1930-1933 (Box 206, Folder 5)
  - Sweden - Swedish, 1938-1950 (Box 206, Folder 6)
  - Sweet, 1940-1948 (Box 206, Folder 7)
  - Swift, 1929-1950 (Box 206, Folder 8)
  - Swift, Harold, 1929-1965 (Box 206, Folder 9)
  - Szilard, Leo and Gertrude, 1953-1975 (Box 206, Folder 10)
  - Tagger, Peter, 1967-1976 (Box 206, Folder 11)
  - Tagger, Peter, 1976-1977 (Box 206, Folder 12)
  - Taylor, 1938-1951 (Box 207, Folder 1)
  - Taylor, Harold, 1959-1961 (Box 207, Folder 2)
  - Teachers, 1933-1950 (Box 207, Folder 3)
  - Teachers Defense Committee, 1954 (Box 207, Folder 4)
  - Teachers Union, 1954-1959 (Box 207, Folder 5)
  - Telegrams, 1936-1937 (Box 207, Folder 6)
  - Temianka, Henri, 1954-1974 (Box 207, Folder 7)
  - Temple, 1938-1948 (Box 207, Folder 8)
  - Tengquist - Tennessee, 1937-1948 (Box 207, Folder 9)
  - Texas, 1938-1951 (Box 207, Folder 10)
  - Third World Power Conference, 1935-1936 (Box 207, Folder 11)
  - Thomas, 1938-1951 (Box 208, Folder 1)
  - Thompson, 1938-1950 (Box 208, Folder 2)
  - Thompson, Bethuel P., 1935-1977 (Box 208, Folder 3)
  - Thompson, Dorothy, 1938-1948 (Box 208, Folder 4)
  - Time Magazine, 1938-1951 (Box 208, Folder 5)
  - Time Magazine, 1954-1955 (Box 208, Folder 6)
  - Time Magazine cover story, 1949-1950 (Box 208, Folder 7)
  - Titus, Charles, 1944-1945 (Box 208, Folder 8)
  - Todd, 1941-1948 (Box 208, Folder 9)
  - Todd, Jessie, 1944-1948 (Box 208, Folder 10)
  - Todd, Jessie, 1948-1950 (Box 208, Folder 11)
  - Todd, Jessie, 1950-1951 (Box 209, Folder 1)
  - Toledo, 1937-1950 (Box 209, Folder 2)
  - Tomlinson, 1942-1944 (Box 209, Folder 3)
  - Tomorrow Magazine, 1943-1949 (Box 209, Folder 4)
  - Torch Honor Society, 1936-1951 (Box 209, Folder 5)
  - Tornay, Stephen C., 1941-1945 (Box 209, Folder 6)
  - Town - Towne, 1938-1951 (Box 209, Folder 7)
  - The Town Hall Club, 1934-1939 (Box 209, Folder 8)
  - The Town Hall Club, 1940-1950 (Box 209, Folder 9)
  - Town Meeting, 1946 [1/2] (Box 209, Folder 10)
  - Town Meeting, 1946 [2/2] (Box 209, Folder 11)
  - Townsley, Elmer R., 1939-1940 (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Travel Center, Inc. (Ralph P. Symons), 1964 (Box 210, Folder 2)
  - Truax, Peggy (Mrs. Chauncey), 1943-1952 (Box 210, Folder 3)
  - Tugwell, Rexford G., 1951-1976 (Box 210, Folder 4)
  - Tulane University, 1936-1950 (Box 210, Folder 5)
  - Tuttle, 1940-1950 (Box 210, Folder 6)
  - Tuttle, Emerson, 1932-1939 (Box 210, Folder 7)
  - Twain, Mark, 1935-1937 (Box 210, Folder 8)
  - Tyler, 1933-1943 (Box 210, Folder 9)
  - Tyler, Ralph W., 1961-1976 (Box 210, Folder 10)
  - Union League Club of Chicago, 1929-1937 (Box 210, Folder 11)
  - Union League Club of Chicago, 1939-1950 (Box 210, Folder 12)
  - United, 1938-1950 (Box 210, Folder 13)
  - United Nations, 1942-1949 (Box 210, Folder 14)
  - United Nations, 1949-1951 (Box 211, Folder 1)
  - United Palestine - U.S.A.A.C., 1932-1938 (Box 211, Folder 2)
  - United States, American Ambulance - U.S. Committee, 1936-1942 (Box 211, Folder 3)
  - United States (Companies), 1938-1950 (Box 211, Folder 4)
  - United States (Government), 1929-1939 (Box 211, Folder 5)
  - United States (Government), 1937-1944 (Box 211, Folder 6)
  - United States (Government), 1945-1948 (Box 211, Folder 7)
  - United States (Government), 1949-1951 (Box 211, Folder 8)
  - United States Junior Chamber of Commerce, 1939-1943 (Box 211, Folder 9)
  - United States Presidency, 1938-1940 (Box 211, Folder 10)
  - United States President's Commission on Higher Education, 1948-1949 (Box 212, Folder 1)
  - United World Federalists, Inc., 1947-1951 (Box 212, Folder 2)
  - University, 1939-1951 (Box 212, Folder 3)
  - University Club (Chicago), 1929-1951 (Box 212, Folder 4)
  - University Club, New York, 1937-1950 (Box 212, Folder 5)
  - University of Chicago - Alumni, 1929-1937 (Box 212, Folder 6)
  - University of Chicago - Alumni, 1937-1950 (Box 212, Folder 7)
  - University of Chicago - Alumni, 1941-1951 (Box 213, Folder 1)
  - University of Chicago - Board of Trustees and committee meetings notices, 1940-1950 (Box 213, Folder 2)
  - University of Chicago - Business, School of, 1934-1951 (Box 213, Folder 3)
  - University of Chicago - "C," Order of, 1933-1946 (Box 213, Folder 4)
  - University of Chicago - Calvert Club, 1949 (Box 213, Folder 5)
  - University of Chicago - Campus Congress Committee, 1938 (Box 213, Folder 6)
  - University of Chicago - Chancellorship, congratulatory letters, 1945-1947 (Box 213, Folder 7)